MAX STEVENS

Frontend Engineer

San Francisco. CA

SUMMARY

Senior front-end developer with seven years of experience in the industry. Seeking to leverage high proficiency in HTML/CSS and Javascript/Typescript frameworks and Saas platforms in a full-time career as a dedicated front-end developer. As I studied UI/UX design, I am always creative and critical in UI development, so I pursue nicelooking and optimized front-end development and used to lead the front-end.

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

07/2016 - 12/2017

FIXER Minato

- Planned, developed, tested, deployed, and maintained web applications.
- Managed front-end development in the company's Portfolio Analyst, Employee Track, and Account Management systems.
- Experience with HTML/CSS, Angular2, Angular6 and React

Senior Frontend Developer

01/2018 - 08/2019

EASTSOURCE

Amsterdam

- Experience various cloud services to integrate with front-end(React|Angular)
- Worked to solve complex problems using the latest in Cloud and Web Technologies.

Frontend Lead Developer

09/2019 - 03/2021

WEBDEVIUM

San Antonio

- Build a minting site generates random NFT arts with Web3.
- Manage configuration of module bundler tools such as Webpack, parcel, etc
- Manage CI/CD setup and configurations, Packaging the app for staging or production, Application versioning and release, Infrastructure configuration and management and Application performance monitoring

Frontend & Blockchain Developer

04/2021 - 05/2022

PORTION

Remote (New York)

- Built NFT Marketplace of digital art on Portion Chain using ERC-721, ERC-1155 both for NFT, ERC-20 for governance token.
- Developed whole smart contract of \$PRT from scratch
- Lead v1 and v2 of Portion front-end development with Web3 and React

EDUCATION

B.S. Computer Science

09/2009 - 06/2013

University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill

Art & Design

09/2013 - 06/2016

Hosei University

SKILLS

HTML · CSS · JavaScript/Typescript · React · Angular · Web3 · Solidity ·

AWS · GCP

LANGUAGES

English Advanced

Japanese Native

HOBBIES



